#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/duongnv23 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Java Software Development Oracle

#### Certifications

Accredited - Confluent Fundamentals for Apache Kafka Spring Professional v5.0 Kotlin for Java Developers Neo4j Certified Professional

# Nguyen Duong

**Spring Professional** 

Hanoi Capital Region

## Summary

Darius Jung is a DDD lover, an event-driven architecture addiction, a practitioner clean series.

With more than 10 years of software development experience, he has worked on monolithic website, micro services, low latency system, high concurrency system, high frequency trading system

## Experience

Techcom Securities Software Engineer May 2020 - Present (1 year 7 months) Hanoi, Thành Phố Hà Nội, Vietnam

- Roles: Senior Software Engineer, DBA, Tech lead, Team lead, Quality Engineer, SA, DevOps

Do any things to make better product:

- Performance testing
- Database optimization: Oracle DB, Oracle timesten, MongoDB, Redis
- Kafka optimization
- Tuning service: configuration, redesign architecture, development
- 2021-04: After 6 month, our trading system has served 300k transactions per day (15 times more than 2020-10).
- 2021-07: We can serves 1M transactions per day: 70 tps for place orders, 500 tps for queries.
- To be a 1st stock broker company in Vietnam. As a leader SE team, I will build a system with 20M transaction per day in 1 year.

Self employed Software Engineer February 2020 - Present (1 year 10 months) Hanoi, Thành Phố Hà Nôi, Vietnam

Served my community

Nexttech Group of Technopreneurs Senior Java Software Engineer November 2016 - January 2020 (3 years 3 months)

Hanoi, Vietnam

- Team Lead at Vaymuon.vn
- Java Technical Lead at Vimo.vn

Viettel Telecom Java Software Engineer August 2013 - July 2016 (3 years) Hanoi, Vietnam

## Education

Hanoi University of Science and Technology
Engineer's degree, Management Information Systems, General · (2008 - 2013)

# Activity

11/01/2021, Viewed by Nga Lê (Lenka)